Guide to the Silliman Lecture Series, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Silliman lecture series, Yale University, records
1996-2002
RU 360
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.81
(15 boxes)
The records consist of audiotapes and videotapes documenting Eugene Shoemaker's 1996 lecture "Near Earth Asteroids and Comets" and James Anderson's 2002 lecture, and photographs and videorecordings documenting the Tercentenary Silliman Memorial Symposium, "A Remembrance of Times Past: The Development of Earth and Its Life."
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-A (YRG 4-A), Records of the Yale secretary's office.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of audiotapes and videotapes documenting Eugene Shoemaker's 1996 lecture "Near Earth Asteroids and Comets" and James Anderson's 2002 lecture, and photographs and videorecordings documenting the Tercentenary Silliman Memorial Symposium, "A Remembrance of Times Past: The Development of Earth and Its Life."
Lectures and lecturing; Audiotapes; Motion pictures (visual works); Videotapes; Shoemaker, E. M. (Eugene Merle), 1928-1997; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Eugene Shoemaker, "Near Earth Asteroids and Comets", 1996; Accession 1997-A-034
  - Eugene Shoemaker, "Near Earth Asteroids and Comets,", 1996 (Box 1)
- Audio and video tapes of James Anderson's Silliman Lectures, 2002; Accession 2007-A-059
  - Videorecordings
    - Lecture 1, 2002 November 4; videotape (DVCAM) (Box 1)
      - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 1U)
    - Lecture 2, 2002 November 5; videotape (DVCAM) (Box 2)
      - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 2U)
    - Lecture 3, 2002 November 6 (Box 3)
      - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 3U)
  - Audiorecordings
    - Lecture 1, 2002 November 4; audiocassette (Box 4)
    - Lecture 2, 2002 November 5; audiocassette (Box 5)
    - Lecture 3, 2002 November 6; audiocassette (Box 6)
- Tercentenary Silliman Memorial Symposium, "A Remembrance of Times Past: The Development of Earth and Its Life", 2001; Accession 2007-A-060
  - Videorecordings
    - Wasserburg, G.L., 2001 September 28; videotape (DVCAM) (Box 1)
    - Cech, Thomas, 2001 September 28; videotape (DVCAM) (Box 2)
    - Schopf, J. William, 2001 September 29; videotape (DVCAM) (Box 3)
    - Leakey, Meare G., 2001 September 29; videotape (DVCAM) (Box 4–5)
    - Allman, John M., 2001 September 29; videotape (DVCAM) (Box 6)
    - Cavalli-Stovza, Luigi Luca, 2001 September 29; videotape (DVCAM) (Box 7)
  - Photographs, 2001 September 28-29 (Box 8, Folder 1)